Great work, you guys.
Cheers!
You saved our butts again today, Rudeus.
That's our quagmire.
No, I'm only any use at all
because you all work so well together already.
And you're always so modest.
Stop!
Since that night in the woods,
I've been working with Counter Arrow almost exclusively.
And my reputation keeps growing.
It's not just the adventurers talking about quagmire Rudeus.
It's the villagers as well.
And one other thing has changed.
Sarah and I have gotten closer.
My dad was a hunter for years before I was born,
so I've basically been practicing archery ever since I could walk.
That's why I still use a bow today.
I know it's not the best for adventuring, but I still like it.
My father was a knight before I was born.
I think he wanted me to be too,
but I always had more talent for magic.
So he hired me a tutor,
a McGurdian mage named Roxy.
That sounds like a woman.
She is.
She was incredible.
And I consider her my master even now.
Oh.
That's neat.
Some topics put her in a sour mood,
but in general, we're good.
Oh, hey, you don't mind if I change the subject, do you?
No.
Well, being a hunter's kid, I'm not too bad with a knife either.
But I mostly use mine to do repairs on my gear.
And the blade is getting awfully chipped.
So, uh, I've been thinking about buying myself a new one pretty soon.
I see.
That being said, if you're free tomorrow, you wanna come shopping with me?
Sure thing.
That sounds like fun.
It's settled then.
And only then did I realize what her invitation really was.
A date.
minute.
Cherry.
Uhm.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Okay.
Hey, wait.
It's all over.
Call us tomorrow.
You can see for the next 10 years is real sleep 2008.
How old were you?
You too, Jason?
Oh.
Yeah.
Hey, my God is a dolmer of only Edison must be gone.
Oh, my God is a dolmer of Lincoln.
He's卡 took me down your sex mode.
Phillip.
Logan Vale is a小時, but we're only a change ofница.
Assault McKарт food.
DJ.
He's a horse, but we're all over the ground today.
I guess that foolsitate me like this.
Oh, man.
Ah! That was so much fun!
Can't afford it now, but seeing all that stuff made me want a new breastplate.
Is something wrong with your current one?
Well... I bought it a long time ago now, so it's starting to get a little tight on me.
Is it now?
Oh, quit blushing, you big baby. I mean, honestly, you men are all the same, huh?
I'm feeling a little tipsy. I almost always drink too much whenever we're together.
Do you?
Yeah, I wonder why. Maybe I just feel safer when you're next to me.
Is this what I think it is? Do I have a shot, as they say? I do, right?
You're allowed to touch me.
Oh, are you sure?
Okay, then. I'll go for it. I've done a lot of reflection in the last 30 seconds, and it's high time I put the pass behind me and moved on.
Hey, why don't we call it a night? It's getting late. I'll walk you to your inn.
On the other hand, I shouldn't try to make a move until I'm positive about this. Isn't that right, Paul?
I think I'd like to talk a little longer.
Uh, if you want. Okay. Maybe we could look for another tavern to try.
Yeah. No. I think I'd rather go back to your room.
Come on. Does she realize how that sounds?
Even if she does, I need to control myself. It's not even like that between us.
But hang on. Read the room. If she's fine with this, maybe I should just go with the flow and let things take their natural course.
Okay, well, let's get going then.
And here we are.
This is a big room.
Would, uh, you like something to drink?
Forget about that. Come over here.
Okay.
Here goes nothing.
So, um...
What's up?
I'm really grateful to you. I almost died. And if you hadn't come looking for me, I definitely would have.
That's why, if you want, we can do it.
Uh...
Ah!
And then it hit me. The real reason I had felt like something was off. It wasn't Sarah. She was amazing. Her body was perfect.
She left absolutely nothing to be desired. The problem was me. My body was raising one hell of a red flag. Or to be more precise, it wasn't raising anything at all.
It was completely unresponsive.
Oh, come on.
Why? How? And since when? How long have I...
This doesn't make any sense. It's never stayed down before, even when I wanted it to.
What in the ever-loving hell is happening to my body?
Hey, it's not like I was... I don't know... into you or anything.
What?
I just... wanted to thank you. You know, pay my debt. So don't go getting the wrong idea. I only came up here because I felt obligated.
You what?
So, bye.
Hey, what a-
What a disaster.
It's cold.
Give me another old man!
Kid, you're gonna hurt yourself drinking like that.
Lay off and pull off, would you?
Well, well. If it isn't quagmire. Fancy seeing you here. Not every day I find you drinking in our favorite tavern.
What are you moping about? Did someone have a shitty day? Come on now, don't bother trying to hide it. I've seen you do this enough.
Whenever something doesn't go your way, you run off with your tail between your legs till it's time to deploy that sad clown smile again.
You're such a-
you asshole!
What are you so mad about? You're always picking fights with me.
Isn't this what you wanted all along?
What are you.
what are you what's wrong with smiling whenever i want huh maybe i should go around insulting and
belittling people just like you if i could get away with that shit if i could stand to make
everyone around me resent me if i didn't care whether i drove everyone away from me if i could
keep your attitude without hating myself then yeah maybe i would i don't want anyone to hate me
that's why i'm always smiling like that what about that pisses you off so much i just want you to stay
smile even if you don't mean it it's not that hard and it hurts when you're so cruel to me
whatever i'm done i don't care anymore so bring it on hate me damn it
have your fucking fun then when i'm sprawled out you can look down on me and laugh
i know i can't take you in a fight
hey soldat it's about time to cut the boy some slack huh yeah i guess so
all right kiddo that was my bad i'm sorry okay maybe you really do have it worse than most
people what would you know about it well nothing yet anyway night storm's on me so drink up and you can
tell me about it it might help you get it off your chest if nothing else
ah so your girl dumped you because you can't get it up
yeah so what you making fun of me now no of course not don't be dumb here's the thing when you're down
in the dumps like this you gotta be clear about why otherwise no one can help make it better
well i was feeling melancholy because don't be so formal you sounded a lot more honest earlier
don't feel like you have to hide behind fancy words like that now start over tell it to me straight
now i was upset about something that happened a long time ago now
i used to know this girl yeah we went through a lot but we got closer and eventually
we were each other's first sure everyone's got to start somewhere that's how it works but in the
morning she had already left gone on some trip and she didn't even tell me where wow she just ditched
you huh hey quit the tears but if that's your reaction i think we just found out what your problem is
why would she leave i thought we were supposed to i don't know well based on my experience it might
have been something you screwed up right beforehand but right beforehand i must have really sucked
no don't start jumping to conclusions let's fix you up but how exactly i don't know but look sometimes
the only way to get past the problem is to keep pounding at it if you get my drift meaning what
it's time to call in a professional
excuse me i am elise it's a pleasure to meet you would you do me the honor of sharing your name sir
oh yeah i'm rudeus a rudeus gray rat i look forward to serving you why don't i get you a drink
your reputation precedes you rudeus does it oh well i suppose another adventurer must have mentioned me
oh no it was my sister you once cast a healing spell on her free of charge
i did you did last winter while you were clearing snow out of the square she said
i'm honored to welcome such a gentleman into my bed the other working girls will be terribly jealous
that's nice may i have another cup yes of course
but our time here is limited so i do help you'll enjoy me as well oh yeah i will thank you
so what do we do just start certainly
now master odious to bed
you can lie back let me get started my way
so then i said you guys go around the back i'll take out all the monsters in the front with one
strike meet me at hey quagmire how'd it go she tried all sorts of different things for me
but no luck ah shoot okay i'm so sorry that i couldn't be of more help hey it's not your fault
you did what you did what you could well i'm out of ideas hey you know him now what do you think
it struck me that he's a bit well frightened and timid around women in general so i wonder if his
partner were someone he didn't have to be afraid of someone whom he feels certain would never turn on
him no matter what then ring any bells for a moment i thought of roxy but now that probably wouldn't work
i fear that such relationships can't be rushed into they must be nurtured little by little
ah figures well drink out tonight quagmire you deserve to forget this right
excuse me sirs we're a bit past closing time
wow it's morning oh well
say quagmire
what i got this rule like when i'm going through a labyrinth i don't rush into things too quickly you
know
because the deeper you go the tougher the monsters you encounter are gonna be different kinds will even
team up with each other sometimes and when that happens you can't just go rushing and blind that's
how people get hurt or dead yeah so what you do is you stay a floor above and ease yourself into things
and that works pretty well yeah fight the weaker ones so with you and sarah i think you just got in too deep
too fast too deep haven't you been listening i mean sure i tried but the problem here is that i didn't
get in at all it's a metaphor because it sounds to me like she was already and raring to go tonight but
maybe you needed more time to get yourself prepped like in your emotion feeling stuff or whatever yeah
i'm not sure about any of that she said she was only doing it out of obligation yeah i hope you're not
always that gullible because from where i've been sitting it looks like she's plenty into you
anyway if you got the time why not go see her again and see if you can't talk things out
sir yes sir yeah maybe i'll go see her tonight or tomorrow or something i don't feel like you're
listening i was actually gonna say yeah whatever i get it already just let it go will ya
but what do i care if it doesn't work out you really think i'd want a woman like her i mean
she's built like a kid a real woman ought to be like elise you know like stacked do you get me
come on soldat am i right or am i right i mean shopping and dinner could you believe all that
little girl crap like are we playing house or what hey quagmire leave it at that i'm just stating facts
rudius deserves a real woman
no sarah i i didn't
you're the worst i never want to see your face again
rudius that was out of line
hold your horses dumbass you go after her right this second and explain yourself okay
stand up idiot go what's the point won't help i don't wanna
don't want to do anything okay then hey why not take a trip to visit your family where's your old man
at huh asura or where milus yeah that's pretty far away isn't it
then you want to come with us huh
a huge labyrinth turned up over in the duchy of near east
we were thinking of heading out sometime today
come on come on it'll be fun why why would you even offer i thought you hated my guts
yeah that creepy smile and that kiss ass attitude really rubbed me the wrong way and i just wanted
you to drop the mask but now that you have and i know what's at the heart of you i know you got
reasons for acting the way you do so there's no reason to hate you now i feel like i've really
misunderstood soldat i've been giving him a wide birth because of my first impression
but he's a much better person than i ever would have imagined so what's the verdict
i'll go please take me with you okay what are we waiting for
Oh, hey, get this.
There's a rumor about some incredible mage who just showed up.
Apparently, he was able to help a party of under 20 people
take down a stray dragon without even breaking a sweat.
Impressive. This guy got a name?
They call him, like, Quagmire Rudeus or something.
Quagmire, huh?
Pardon me, gentlemen. Would you mind telling me more?
Uh, more about what?
This rumor about the adventurer.
Quagmire Rudeus, was it?
But that's pretty much it.
I don't actually know anything else about him.
Come on, think harder.
Surely you can remember a little more.
There's something good in it for you and your friend there if you do.
Yeah, I know. He's in Pippin.
Bacheron Second City Pippin.
Is he really?
Thank you so much.
So I finally found him.
I am.